<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tasty AF</title>
    <link>https://andrewalexander.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Tasty AF</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 22:01:42 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andrewalexander.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mediterranean Couscous Salad - serves 4-6</title>
      <link>https://andrewalexander.github.io/posts/mediterranean-couscous-salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 22:01:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewalexander.github.io/posts/mediterranean-couscous-salad/</guid>
      <description>The salad is great as a standalone dish but also complements many other dishes, especially some grilled/cast iron salmon. There&amp;rsquo;s not much else to say here - if you have a craving for some mediterranean cuisine, it definitely scratches that itch.
This stuff keeps pretty well - it does great as a side for lunch the next day as well. The flavors really get to know each other even better overnight and it doesn&amp;rsquo;t get as soggy as you might thing with all the wetter ingredients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turkey Quinoa Meatloaf - serves 2-4</title>
      <link>https://andrewalexander.github.io/posts/turkey-quinoa-meatloaf/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 21:59:21 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewalexander.github.io/posts/turkey-quinoa-meatloaf/</guid>
      <description>This is known as &amp;ldquo;Andrew&amp;rsquo;s infamous turkey quinoa meatloaf&amp;rdquo;. It was the first thing Andrew cooked for Tiyrah that actually impressed her. It remains a delicacy in the AF household. Even if you don&amp;rsquo;t like quinoa or think that ground turkey has no place in meatloaf, you will be amazed by this dish. It says it serves 2-4&amp;hellip; Sometimes it&amp;rsquo;s hard to stop ourselves. Your results may vary.
Things to watch out for/take note of:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tomato and Pickled Beet Salad - serves 4</title>
      <link>https://andrewalexander.github.io/posts/pickled-beet-salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 21:58:12 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewalexander.github.io/posts/pickled-beet-salad/</guid>
      <description>This has no business being as good as it is for how simple and quick it is to make. Seriously. We didn&amp;rsquo;t even know if we liked pickled beets but after this&amp;hellip; we are convinced. The feta complements the beet and balsamic flavor perfectly.
Things to watch out for/take note of:
Pickled beets are hard to find sometimes. Look near pickles and olives in the grocery store. Make sure to get them sliced or do a lot more slicing later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grit Bowl - serves 2</title>
      <link>https://andrewalexander.github.io/posts/grit-bowl/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 21:54:24 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewalexander.github.io/posts/grit-bowl/</guid>
      <description>This is a go-to we eat literally every week. Sometimes multiple times a week. It will keep us both full for hours, and is something we make when we know it will be a long day. It&amp;rsquo;s not too prep-heavy but if cutting up onions and garlic really is too much to do in the AM, some granulated onion and garlic can be substituted in with decent success.
Things to watch out for/take note of:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bimbimbap - serves 6 (or 2-3 very hungry people)</title>
      <link>https://andrewalexander.github.io/posts/bimbimbap/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 21:46:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewalexander.github.io/posts/bimbimbap/</guid>
      <description>We first made this recipe as a special request from a friend we were having over for dinner. She knew we loved to cook and decided to take us up on that. Well as it turned out, we loved it so much we ended up making it again with chicken the next night! Any time we remember this recipe it ends up getting cooked that night. It is also a go-to whenever we have house guests now since we get to flex a little bit.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
